[car engine revving]
[Aceleración del motor del coche]
[dog barking]
[ladridos de perro]
[slurping]
[sorbiendo]
[car engine shuts off]
[El motor del coche se apaga]
[car door opens]
[Se abre la puerta del coche]
Hey, come here. Help me take care of this.
Oye, ven aquí. Ayúdame a solucionar esto.
[Farmer exhales]
[El granjero exhala]
[Farmer] What is this? You didn't chop it up?
[Agricultor] ¿Qué es esto? ¿No lo has troceado?
What am I supposed to do with it?
¿Qué se supone que debo hacer con esto?
Well, I got into some shit. Help a brother out.
Bueno, me metí en un lío. Ayúdenme, por favor.
Nobody told me.
Nadie me lo dijo.
You're from Yes Money?
¿Eres de Yes Money?
Course I am. We've met a few times already.
Por supuesto que sí. Ya nos hemos visto un par de veces.
Moonsu and the other guys aren't with you?
¿Moonsu y los demás no están contigo?
Moonsu?
¿Luna?
Moonsu's probably at work right now. Duh.
Moonsu probablemente esté trabajando ahora mismo. Obvio.
[exhales sharply]
[exhala bruscamente]
[Woogy] Just do me this favor.
[Woogy] Solo hazme este favor.
[exhales]
[exhala]
[Farmer grunts]
[Gruñidos del granjero]
[Farmer] Who the fuck brings uncut meat?
[Granjero] ¿Quién carajo trae carne sin cortar?
[bag scraping]
[raspado de bolsa]
I appreciate this!
¡Lo agradezco!
[machine buzzing and clanging]
[zumbido y ruido metálico de la máquina]
[bones crunching]
[crujido de huesos]
[pigs snorting]
[cerdos resoplando]
[slop squelching]
[chapoteo de lodo]
[crows cawing]
[cuervos graznando]
[Heeju breathing heavily]
[Heeju respira con dificultad]
[knock at door]
[Llaman a la puerta]
[gasps]
[jadeos]
[knocking continues]
[Los golpes en la puerta continúan]
[door creaks]
[La puerta cruje]
HAENGBOK PAWNSHOP
CASA DE EMPEÑO HAENGBOK
Heeju.
Ey.
I'm hungry.
Tengo hambre.
[chuckles]
[risitas]
[Woogy] Oh, I'm so fucking starving right now!
[Woogy] ¡Oh, me muero de hambre ahora mismo!
[Woogy groans]
[Woogy gime]
[door locks]
[cerraduras de puertas]
[broth splashing]
[salpicaduras de caldo]
[exhales heavily]
[exhala profundamente]
[slurping]
[sorbiendo]
[slurping continues]
[continúa el sorbo]
[huffing]
[resoplando]
[Woogy slurping]
[Woogy sorbiendo]
[Woogy exhales]
[Woogy exhala]
Ah.
Ah.
[exhales]
[exhala]
Heeju.
Ey.
You know, my dad...
Ya sabes, mi papá...
...he was the same kind of asshole as your uncle.
...era el mismo tipo de imbécil que tu tío.
He brought our whole family down with his gambling addiction.
Su adicción al juego arruinó a toda nuestra familia .
That piece of shit should have just died alone.
Ese pedazo de mierda debería haberse muerto solo.
He even tried to kill my mom and I.
Incluso intentó matarnos a mi madre y a mí.
Anyway...
De todos modos...
[Woogy] Don't give it another though.
[Woogy] No le des otra oportunidad.
[Woogy] I took care of the body.
[Woogy] Yo cuidé el cuerpo.
[Woogy] There's not a single shred of flesh left.
[Woogy] No queda ni un solo trozo de carne.
Don't worry about it.
No te preocupes por eso.
[grunts]
[gruñidos]
This one? This one's mine?
¿Este? ¿Este es mío?
I said don't worry!
¡Te dije que no te preocupes!
Just let it go.
Déjalo ir.
[smacks lips]
[Se relame los labios]
[Woogy] I mean, that was a man who deserved to die.
[Woogy] Quiero decir, ese era un hombre que merecía morir.
[Heeju] A man who deserved to die?
[Heeju] ¿Un hombre que merecía morir?
[Woogy] Mm-hmm.
[Woogy] Mm-hmm.
[exhales]
[exhala]
Hey.
Ey.
You see how important money is now? STYLE ::cue()
¿Ves lo importante que es el dinero ahora? ESTILO ::cue()
It makes the world go 'round.
Hace que el mundo gire.
Like, having money lets you do anything you could ever want.
Es decir, tener dinero te permite hacer todo lo que puedas desear.
[Woogy] And it also lets you not do things you don't want.
[Woogy] Y también te permite no hacer cosas que no quieres.
[Woogy] Oh, yeah.
[Woogy] Oh, sí.
[Woogy] Here you go. As promised.
[Woogy] Aquí tienes. Como prometí.
[Woogy] Your new ID card.
[Woogy] Tu nueva tarjeta de identificación.
RESIDENT REGISTRATION CARD JU HARAN
TARJETA DE REGISTRO DE RESIDENTE JU HARAN
I just went through all our debtors,
Acabo de revisar todos nuestros deudores,
and then I picked out who looked like you the most.
y luego elegí a la persona que más se parecía a ti.
[Woogy] We can take care of the passport and fingerprints and all that later.
[Woogy] Podemos ocuparnos del pasaporte , las huellas dactilares y todo eso más tarde.
[Woogy] But for starters, open a bank account under her name.
[Woogy] Pero para empezar, abre una cuenta bancaria a su nombre.
Well, obviously we're about to have piles of cash rollin' in.
Bueno, obviamente estamos a punto de empezar a recibir montones de dinero.
So, can't exactly keep it all piled up in here.
Así que, no puedo tenerlo todo amontonado aquí.
Hmm?
¿Mmm?
Who is this lady?
¿Quién es esta señora?
[Woogy] Ah, this lady...
[Woogy] Ah, esta señora...
...she's dead.
...ella está muerta.
It was suicide.
Fue un suicidio.
A year ago.
Hace un año.
So they say.
Eso dicen.
[Woogy] She doesn't exist in the world anymore.
[Woogy] Ella ya no existe en el mundo.
No one is looking for her, and there's no way to find her.
Nadie la busca y no hay manera de encontrarla.
[Woogy] And someone that young...
[Woogy] Y alguien tan joven...
...you really think she had any money? They took her organs.
¿De verdad crees que tenía dinero? Le extrajeron los órganos.
[Woogy] She just doesn't exist. She's gone.
[Woogy] Ella simplemente no existe. Se ha ido.
I'll also turn out like that, if I get caught by your company people.
Yo también acabaré así si me pillan los de tu empresa.
So be good.
Así que pórtate bien.
Or else.
Si no.
[chuckles]
[risitas]
Anyway, we need to wrap this whole thing up quickly.
En fin, tenemos que terminar con todo esto rápidamente.
[Woogy] Since Detective Kim is even involved now,
[Woogy] Ya que el detective Kim está involucrado ahora,
it's a huge deal.
Es algo muy importante.
I bet the guys at Yes Money are desperate to find you.
Apuesto a que los de Yes Money están desesperados por encontrarte.
What do we do?
¿Qué hacemos?
[Woogy] We got eight potatoes left, right?
[Woogy] Nos quedan ocho patatas, ¿verdad?
Let's craft and sell two at a time now.
Ahora vamos a fabricar y vender dos a la vez.
After selling so many one-kilo bars, I realized how fucking easy it is.
Después de vender tantas barras de un kilo, me di cuenta de lo jodidamente fácil que es.
If I just run my ass off,
Si simplemente me muero de ganas de correr,
hitting all the jewelry shops,
visitando todas las joyerías,
I can sell 20 in three days.
Puedo vender 20 en tres días.
[Woogy] It could be done in two weeks.
[Woogy] Se podría hacer en dos semanas.
[Woogy] In the meantime,
[Woogy] Mientras tanto,
you should get your passport ready to go.
Debes tener tu pasaporte listo para partir.
Then we'll go overseas. Simple.
Entonces nos iremos al extranjero. Así de simple.
What is it?
¿Qué es?
You still don't trust me after all this?
¿Todavía no confías en mí después de todo esto?
[Woogy] Heeju.
[Woogy] Heeju.
[Woogy] We're way past being just business partners now.
[Woogy] Ya hemos superado la etapa de ser solo socios comerciales.
I even killed a man because of you.
Incluso maté a un hombre por tu culpa.
We're like bound by fate now.
Ahora estamos unidos por el destino.
[chuckles]
[risitas]
Bound by fate.
Unidos por el destino.
[Woogy chuckles]
[Woogy se ríe entre dientes]
[Woogy] I better get going.
[Woogy] Mejor me voy.
How many potatoes are you bringing next round?
¿Cuántas patatas vas a traer la próxima vez?
Two.
Dos.
Correct. Where do they need to go?
Correcto. ¿Adónde tienen que ir?
To the shop.
A la tienda.
Correct. Where do you get those?
Correcto. ¿Dónde se consiguen?
I guess not. Okay.
Supongo que no. De acuerdo.
You're too smart!
¡Eres demasiado inteligente!
I'm out.
Me voy.
Ah, fuck, I'm so tired.
Ah, joder, estoy tan cansado.
[Woogy chuckles]
[Woogy se ríe entre dientes]
[door creaks closed]
[La puerta cruje al cerrarse]
[distant car engine rumbling]
[sonido lejano de un motor de coche]
[clock ticking echoing]
[el tictac del reloj resuena]
[♪ sad piano music]
[♪ Música triste de piano]
[♪ music continues]
[♪ La música continúa]
EPISODE 5 SECRET
EPISODIO 5 SECRETO
JANGGAK TRADE INC.
JANGGAK COMERCIO INC.
[Donggu] Can I help you?
[Donggu] ¿Puedo ayudarle?
Uh, hi. I want to buy a car today.
Hola. Quiero comprar un coche hoy.
You're here to get a car?
¿Vienes a comprar un coche?
-[Heeju] Yes. -Ah.
-[Heeju] Sí. -Ah.
How did you hear about us?
¿Cómo se enteró de nosotros?
I run a pawnshop.
Tengo una casa de empeños.
You run a pawnshop?
¿Tienes una casa de empeños?
-[grunts] -[Donggu] All right.
-[gruñidos] -[Donggu] Muy bien.
Let me show you our cars.
Déjame mostrarte nuestros coches.
-Okay. -Any particular type car you had in mind?
-De acuerdo. -¿Tenías en mente algún tipo de coche en particular?
Uh, no, not really.
Eh, no, en realidad no.
No, okay then.
No, está bien entonces.
Well, if that's the case,
Bueno, si ese es el caso,
then this one here is probably what you're looking for.
Entonces, probablemente este de aquí es lo que estás buscando.
[Donggu] It has good mileage, plus it's practically brand new.
[Donggu] Tiene un buen kilometraje, además está prácticamente nuevo.
Huh.
Eh.
[machine rattling]
[ruido de máquina]
[Donggu] Now all you gotta do is take this to the district office
[Donggu] Ahora solo tienes que llevar esto a la oficina del distrito.
and transfer the title.
y transferir la titularidad.
-Okay. -Here. STYLE ::cue()
-De acuerdo. -Aquí. ESTILO ::cue()
-You can take the car today. -Thanks.
-Puedes llevarte el coche hoy. -Gracias.
Actually, I was curious about your pawnshop.
En realidad, tenía curiosidad por su casa de empeños.
[stammers]
[tartamudea]
Is it here around the Jeongsan area?
¿Está por aquí, cerca de la zona de Jeongsan?
[exhales]
[exhala]
Why do you ask?
¿Por qué lo preguntas?
It's just that there's not a pawnshop I don't know around here.
Es que no conozco ninguna casa de empeños por aquí.
It was originally run by a relative, and something came up,
Originalmente lo dirigía un familiar, y surgió algo,
so I ended up taking it over.
Así que terminé haciéndome cargo.
Ah.
Ah.
I was wondering, where do all the cars end up going?
Me preguntaba, ¿adónde acaban todos los coches?
Most of 'em? Eh...
¿La mayoría de ellos? Eh...
[Donggu] Most of 'em end up overseas.
[Donggu] La mayoría de ellos terminan en el extranjero.
What about the other collateral, besides the cars?
¿Qué hay de las demás garantías, además de los coches?
Those other items normally end up overseas, too.
Esos otros artículos también suelen acabar en el extranjero.
More or less.
Más o menos.
[Heeju] You only ship items overseas and don't ship anything back in?
[Heeju] ¿Solo envías artículos al extranjero y no haces envíos de vuelta?
For a young lady, you sure are curious about all this.
Para ser una señorita, sin duda sientes curiosidad por todo esto.
-Uh... -[Donggu] I mean,
-Eh... -[Donggu] Quiero decir,
you're askin' a lot of questions.
Estás haciendo muchas preguntas.
Are you a cop or someone from customs?
¿Eres policía o alguien de aduanas?
No, it's nothing like that. I'm just really curious.
No, no es nada de eso. Simplemente tengo mucha curiosidad.
Actually, up until recently,
En realidad, hasta hace poco,
I used to be in a similar line of work as you.
Yo también trabajaba en un sector similar al tuyo.
Checking imported goods, clearing them for entry.
Inspeccionar las mercancías importadas y autorizar su entrada al país.
Oh, really?
¿Ah, de verdad?
Uh, one more thing.
Eh, una cosa más.
We've had this for a while, just hanging around the pawnshop.
Lo tenemos desde hace un tiempo, simplemente merodeando por la casa de empeños.
[Heeju] And I was wondering if you had any bullets for it.
[Heeju] Y me preguntaba si tenías alguna bala para eso.
It's just sometimes working late nights alone can be kinda scary.
A veces, trabajar hasta tarde sola puede dar un poco de miedo.
[Heeju] Hopefully I never have to use it,
[Heeju] Ojalá nunca tenga que usarlo,
but just having it would make me feel so much safer.
Pero el simple hecho de tenerlo me haría sentir mucho más segura.
Yeah. Is that so?
Sí. ¿Es así?
You're a surprising young lady.
Eres una joven sorprendente.
I can give you however much you want.
Puedo darte lo que quieras.
[Donggu] It's not about the money.
[Donggu] No se trata del dinero.
Smuggling is just not what I do.
El contrabando no es lo mío.
Is it that you can't, or that you won't?
¿Es que no puedes, o es que no quieres?
[Donggu chuckles nervously]
[Donggu ríe nerviosamente]
Listen, I'm guessing since you're new in town,
Escucha, supongo que ya que eres nuevo en la ciudad,
you haven't heard of me before.
Nunca habías oído hablar de mí.
Do I look like someone who can't to you?
¿Acaso parezco alguien que no puede?
Maybe I just don't wanna.
Tal vez simplemente no quiero.
I was thinking if you could get this for me,
Estaba pensando si podrías conseguirme esto,
then there could be other things you could help me with.
Entonces podría haber otras cosas en las que podrías ayudarme.
[inhales sharply]
[inhala bruscamente]
However, if it's something that you don't do, then...
Sin embargo, si es algo que no haces, entonces...
What other sort of things did you need help with?
¿En qué otro tipo de cosas necesitabas ayuda?
Well, I don't know.
Bueno, no lo sé.
There's nothing that a pawnshop doesn't have.
No hay nada que no se pueda encontrar en una casa de empeño.
Detonics.
Detónica.
Wait here a second while I go get them for you.
Espera aquí un segundo mientras voy a buscarlos.
[door opens and shuts]
[La puerta se abre y se cierra]
[inhales and exhales sharply]
[inhala y exhala bruscamente]
[Donggu breathing heavily]
[Donggu respira con dificultad]
[grunts]
[gruñidos]
So, have you fired a gun?
¿Has disparado alguna vez un arma?
Uh, no.
Eh, no.
It's not like I'd actually have a reason to use it.
No es que realmente tuviera una razón para usarlo.
Uh-huh.
Ajá.
First insert the magazine.
Primero inserta el cargador.
[magazine clicks]
[clics de revista]
[Donggu] Like that. After that,
[Donggu] Así. Después de eso,
you grab this part and slide it back.
Agarra esta parte y deslízala hacia atrás.
[Donggu] When you do that,
[Donggu] Cuando haces eso,
a bullet will be chambered here.
Aquí se introducirá una bala en la recámara.
And since it's very dangerous,
Y puesto que es muy peligroso,
you need to always keep the safety up,
Siempre debes mantener la seguridad en alto,
like so, until you need to fire.
así, hasta que necesites disparar.
It's the same with the trigger.
Lo mismo ocurre con el gatillo.
Until you're ready, your finger stays back here.
Hasta que estés listo, tu dedo se queda aquí.
[Donggu] And when you shoot,
[Donggu] Y cuando disparas,
always hold it with both hands.
Sujétalo siempre con ambas manos.
Just like so.
Así mismo.
[Donggu] Most women find the recoil pretty strong.
[Donggu] La mayoría de las mujeres encuentran el retroceso bastante fuerte.
You see this? This waving?
¿Ves esto? ¿Este saludo?
Any sort of movement affects your accuracy.
Cualquier tipo de movimiento afecta a tu precisión.
[Donggu] The head and heart.
[Donggu] La cabeza y el corazón.
That's where you aim, and if you don't hit them there,
Ahí es donde apuntas, y si no les das ahí,
you keep shooting until they're dead.
Sigues disparando hasta que estén muertos.
-Bang! - [gasps]
-¡Bang! - [jadeos]
[Donggu] Bang, bang. Bang, bang.
[Donggu] Bang, bang. Bang, bang.
You want to kill, you keep shooting.
Si quieres matar, sigue disparando.
Here.
Aquí.
How much money do I owe you?
¿Cuánto dinero te debo?
Ah, no, no, no, no.
Ah, no, no, no, no.
I don't need money. It's a gift from me to you.
No necesito dinero. Es un regalo mío para ti.
In return, how about from now on, you only work with me?
A cambio, ¿qué te parece si, a partir de ahora, solo trabajas conmigo?
[car engine rumbling]
[sonido de motor de coche]
[clicks tongue]
[chasquea la lengua]
[exhales]
[exhala]
NAME JU HARAN STYLE ::cue()
NOMBRE JU HARAN ESTILO ::cue()
[♪ dramatic piano music]
[♪ Música dramática para piano]
[shovel digging]
[excavando con pala]
[grunts]
[gruñidos]
[Heeju grunts]
[Heeju abajo]
[gold bars clinking]
[sonido de lingotes de oro]
[Heeju grunting]
[Heeju gruñe]
[Heeju] There's no one in this world who deserves to die.
[Heeju] No hay nadie en este mundo que merezca morir.
I killed so I can live.
Maté para poder vivir.
That's all it is.
Eso es todo.
[groans]
[gemidos]
[Heeju] Because I can't be the one to die.
[Heeju] Porque no puedo ser yo quien muera.
[blows hard]
[sopla fuerte]
[exhales]
[exhala]
[Heeju grunts]
[Heeju abajo]
[breathing heavily]
[respirando con dificultad]
[car engine rumbling]
[sonido de motor de coche]
[grunts]
[gruñidos]
[breathing heavily]
[respirando con dificultad]
[brakes squeak]
[chirrido de frenos]
GANGWON SAEBAEK HOSPITAL
HOSPITAL GANGWON SAEBAEK
-[Sunok exhales] -[Heeju] Auntie.
-[Sunok exhala] -[Heeju] Tía.
[Heeju] How are you doing?
[Heeju] ¿Cómo estás?
[Sunok grunts]
[El suelo tiembla]
-[Sunok groans lightly] -Yes?
-[Sunok gime levemente] -¿Sí?
[Sunok exhales]
[Sunok exhala]
[Sunok] Why are you still here?
[Sunok] ¿Por qué sigues aquí?
You should lie down.
Deberías acostarte.
The cash I gave you.
El dinero que te di.
Did you return it?
¿Lo devolviste?
Is that...
¿Es eso...?
[Sunok] ...why he dropped the charges?
[Sunok] ...¿por qué retiró los cargos?
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm.
[Sunok] You crazy bitch.
[Sunok] Perra loca.
Why didn't you run when I told you to?
¿Por qué no corriste cuando te lo dije?
[shudders]
[escalofríos]
You need to run away.
Tienes que huir.
Go quickly, before he comes back.
Vete rápido, antes de que vuelva.
It's all right.
Está bien.
That man won't ever come back again.
Ese hombre no volverá jamás.
I'm telling you, he will!
¡Te lo aseguro, lo hará!
And then the both of us will be trapped here.
Y entonces los dos quedaremos atrapados aquí.
He's already bleeding me dry. That's more than enough.
Ya me está dejando en la ruina. Con eso basta.
You-you have to go now.
Tienes que irte ahora.
I don't have to.
No tengo por qué hacerlo.
It's not like I have much time left. I don't need you. Just hurry up and go.
No es que me quede mucho tiempo. No te necesito. Date prisa y vete.
Aunty, that's why I'm not leaving you.
Tía, por eso no te voy a dejar.
What'll it take, then? Should I hang myself?
¿Qué tengo que hacer entonces? ¿ Debería ahorcarme?
-[Sunok] Listen to me! -No!
-[Sunok] ¡Escúchame! -¡No!
[distant footsteps approaching]
[Pasos lejanos que se acercan]
He has to be coming.
Tiene que venir.
He's coming, I said!
¡Ya viene!, dije.
You-you need to hide somewhere.
Tú... necesitas esconderte en algún lugar.
-Look at me. Stop. -[Sunok] Quickly.
-Mírame. Detente. -[Sunok] Rápido.
-You have to hide- -[Heeju] Auntie. Auntie. Auntie.
-Tienes que esconderte- -[Heeju] Tía. Tía. Tía.
That asshole is never coming back.
Ese imbécil no va a volver jamás.
He can't come back.
Él no puede regresar.
[Heeju exhales deeply]
[Heeju exhala profundamente]
This time I made sure of that so now...
Esta vez me aseguré de ello, así que ahora...
...everything's gonna be okay.
...todo va a estar bien.
From now on, I'll stay by your side.
De ahora en adelante, me quedaré a tu lado.
[Sunok inhales and exhales deeply] STYLE ::cue()
[Sunok inhala y exhala profundamente] ESTILO ::cue()
[distant sirens wailing]
[Sirenas aullando a lo lejos]
[Thai Businessman] My chairman's losing patience now.
[Empresario tailandés] Mi presidente está perdiendo la paciencia.
All these construction delays.
Todos estos retrasos en la construcción.
[Woojin speaking Korean]
[Woojin hablando coreano]
[speaking Korean]
[hablando coreano]
There are formal legal protocols to follow.
Existen protocolos legales formales que deben seguirse.
Once your chairman signs off, we're ready to move immediately.
Una vez que su presidente dé su aprobación, estaremos listos para actuar de inmediato.
Well, for that to happen,
Bueno, para que eso suceda,
we're going to need a solid guarantee from you guys.
Vamos a necesitar una garantía sólida de su parte.
[speaking Korean]
[hablando coreano]
[Thai Businessman] Let's just say we'll need a reason to move.
[Empresario tailandés] Digamos que necesitaremos una razón para mudarnos.
[speaking Korean]
[hablando coreano]
What did he just say?
¿Qué acaba de decir?
He wishes to speak with your chairman directly.
Desea hablar directamente con su presidente.
No, what'd he say before that?
No, ¿qué dijo antes?
[Gyuseok speaking Korean]
[Gyuseok hablando coreano]
[speaking Korean]
[hablando coreano]
[Woojin] The chairman says,
[Woojin] El presidente dice:
"The coffin in Korea's now your responsibility.
"El ataúd en Corea ahora es tu responsabilidad."
So you will have to move it yourself."
Así que tendrás que moverlo tú mismo.
[speaking Korean]
[hablando coreano]
[chopsticks clatter on plate]
[Los palillos chocan contra el plato]
Something like this isn't complete without a drink.
Algo así no está completo sin una bebida.
My chairman told me...
Mi presidente me dijo...
...to take extra special care of you.
...para cuidarte de forma muy especial.
He's committing everything to this deal.
Está apostando todo a este acuerdo.
[Woojin speaking Korean]
[Woojin hablando coreano]
[speaking Korean]
[hablando coreano]
[exhales sharply]
[exhala bruscamente]
How's it goin'?
¿Cómo te va?
Dokyung hasn't opened his mouth yet?
¿Dokyung aún no ha abierto la boca?
[snaps fingers]
[chasquea los dedos]
[Hocheol] I'm sorry.
[Hocheol] Lo siento.
[Gyuseok] Hocheol, come on.
[Gyuseok] Hocheol, vamos.
[lighter flicks]
[movimientos de encendedor]
Didn't you tell me not to worry?
¿No me dijiste que no me preocupara?
You said that bastard has nowhere to run and that he's in your hands.
Dijiste que ese bastardo no tiene a dónde huir y que está en tus manos.
[Gyuseok] So what now?
[Gyuseok] ¿Y ahora qué?
[Hocheol] I'll go to the hospital myself, then I'll shut him up.
[Hocheol] Iré yo mismo al hospital y allí lo haré callar.
[Gyuseok] How, exactly? You said the cops are involved.
[Gyuseok] ¿Cómo, exactamente? Dijiste que la policía está involucrada.
[Hocheol] I know a detective at the Gangwon Central Police Department.
[Hocheol] Conozco a un detective del Departamento de Policía Central de Gangwon.
I might need to buy a little time to have a moment alone with Dokyung.
Quizás necesite ganar un poco de tiempo para estar a solas con Dokyung.
[Gyuseok] And what if he still doesn't talk?
[Gyuseok] ¿Y si sigue sin hablar?
Kill him?
¿Matarlo?
How would we find the casket?
¿Cómo encontraríamos el ataúd?
[Hocheol] Worst-case scenario.
[Hocheol] El peor escenario posible.
Even if we have to give up the casket, shutting him up is the priority.
Aunque tengamos que renunciar al ataúd, lo prioritario es hacerlo callar.
Ah.
Ah.
Is that right?
¿Es correcto?
That's the priority?
¿Esa es la prioridad?
[Gyuseok] I didn't realize that.
[Gyuseok] No me había dado cuenta.
Hey, Hocheol.
Hola, Hocheol.
[cigarette hissing] STYLE ::cue()
[silbido de cigarrillo] ESTILO ::cue()
Are you the boss now?
¿Ahora eres el jefe?
[Gyuseok] Do you get to decide what's important?
[Gyuseok] ¿Tú decides qué es importante?
I'm sorry.
Lo lamento.
I spoke out of turn.
Hablé fuera de turno.
[Gyuseok] This bastard Lee Dokyung, he married?
[Gyuseok] ¿Este bastardo de Lee Dokyung se casó?
As far as I know, he's not married.
Que yo sepa, no está casado.
Hocheol, listen.
Hocheol, escucha.
Cut off a finger from a friend or a bitch close to him
Córtale un dedo a un amigo o a una zorra cercana a él.
and send it to him.
y envíaselo.
You think he won't talk after that?
¿Crees que no volverá a hablar después de eso?
Yes, I'll get on that right away.
Sí, me pondré con eso de inmediato.
When you find the casket, don't open it right away.
Cuando encuentres el ataúd, no lo abras de inmediato.
Give me a call first.
Llámame primero.
I want to go check it myself.
Quiero ir a comprobarlo yo mismo.
[Hocheol] Yes, sir.
[Hocheol] Sí, señor.
Hocheol, make sure you get this right.
Hocheol, asegúrate de hacerlo bien.
[exhales]
[exhala]
[Gyuseok] That casket better be sitting in
[Gyuseok] Más vale que ese ataúd esté sentado en
the hotel before I get back from this trip.
el hotel antes de que regrese de este viaje.
Understand?
¿Entender?
Right.
Bien.
But sir.
Pero señor.
That cask-
Ese barril-
[phone beeps]
[El teléfono emite pitidos]
[♪ suspenseful music]
[♪ música de suspense]
AHN GYUSEOK
AHN GYUSEOK
[door opens and closes]
[La puerta se abre y se cierra]
FIELD INVESTIGATION REPORT
INFORME DE INVESTIGACIÓN DE CAMPO
[Jinman] So it turns out the window on the driver's side
[Jinman] Resulta que por la ventana del lado del conductor
of the van was slightly open.
La furgoneta estaba ligeramente abierta.
It's lucky I caught that, which is pretty genius, don't you think?
¡Qué suerte que lo capté! Es bastante ingenioso, ¿no crees?
Yeah?
¿Sí?
It's pretty dark, but take a look.
Está bastante oscuro, pero échale un vistazo.
[Jinman] You see it?
[Jinman] ¿Lo ves?
[Jinman] Can you make it out?
[Jinman] ¿Puedes entenderlo?
See? It's a woman.
¿Lo ves? Es una mujer.
[Jinman] And out of all the witnesses involved in
[Jinman] Y de entre todos los testigos involucrados en
the smuggling case who were questioned by the police,
el caso de contrabando que fueron interrogados por la policía,
there was only one woman who had been on National Route 6 that day.
Solo había una mujer que había estado en la Ruta Nacional 6 ese día.
And even better, she was caught by surveillance cameras.
Y lo que es aún mejor, fue captada por cámaras de vigilancia.
All right, so who is she?
Muy bien, ¿quién es ella?
I can let you know soon.
Te lo haré saber pronto.
I'll even find that casket, too.
También encontraré ese ataúd.
[Jinman] I just don't have any hard evidence yet. Okay?
[Jinman] Simplemente no tengo ninguna prueba contundente todavía. ¿De acuerdo?
I don't wanna cause problems by barking up the wrong tree.
No quiero causar problemas por equivocarme de tema.
[Hocheol] Hard evidence?
[Hocheol] ¿Pruebas contundentes?
It's not like we're running a police investigation here.
No es que estemos llevando a cabo una investigación policial.
Maybe, but I'm still a cop, aren't I?
Tal vez, pero sigo siendo policía, ¿no?
Cut the crap and tell me who the woman is now.
Déjate de tonterías y dime quién es esa mujer.
[scoffs]
[se burla]
Here.
Aquí.
[clears throat]
[Se aclara la garganta]
[Jinman] Head of Gangwon Security, Cha Yujin.
[Jinman] Jefe de seguridad de Gangwon, Cha Yujin.
[Jinman] There's a good chance she's Lee Dokyung's accomplice.
[Jinman] Hay muchas probabilidades de que sea cómplice de Lee Dokyung.
I already planted a tracking device on her car,
Ya le puse un dispositivo de rastreo en su auto,
so don't worry about that, 'kay?
Así que no te preocupes por eso, ¿de acuerdo?
Once they head to Jeongsan, we just follow 'em. Simple.
Una vez que se dirigen a Jeongsan, simplemente los seguimos. Así de simple.
When?
¿Cuando?
She'll go sooner or later.
Tarde o temprano se irá.
She has to. The casket's there.
Tiene que hacerlo. El ataúd está ahí.
'Kay, good work.
Vale, buen trabajo.
Do you wanna be paid in cash, or do you want chips?
¿Quieres que te paguen en efectivo o prefieres fichas?
I'll take chips.
Tomaré papas fritas.
I'll have a table set up tomorrow. Just use 100.
Mañana tendré una mesa preparada. Solo usa 100.
But I haven't found the casket yet.
Pero aún no he encontrado el ataúd.
That's enough for now. I'll take care of the rest.
Por ahora es suficiente. Yo me encargo del resto.
Ah.
Ah.
Don't mention the gold.
No menciones el oro.
We should pretend we don't know. Even around the chairman.
Deberíamos fingir que no lo sabemos. Incluso delante del presidente.
[Hocheol] Actually, you know what? Now that I think about it...
[Hocheol] En realidad, ¿sabes qué? Ahora que lo pienso...
...if the chairman were to find out you and I know about the gold...
...si el presidente se enterara de que tú y yo sabemos lo del oro...
...well, who knows what could happen?
...bueno, ¿quién sabe lo que podría pasar?
[Hocheol] I'm sure he didn't tell us for a reason.
[Hocheol] Estoy seguro de que no nos lo dijo por alguna razón.
Is that right? So that's how it's gonna go.
¿Es correcto? Así es como va a ser.
I guess that's how it is, then. Wow.
Supongo que así son las cosas, entonces. Vaya.
[Jinman] Knowing Chairman Ahn,
[Jinman] Conociendo al Presidente Ahn,
it couldn't have been easy trusting someone with all that gold.
No debió ser fácil confiarle todo ese oro a alguien.
[Jinman] Even if they were family.
[Jinman] Incluso si fueran familia.
[Jinman] That's hard to do. Yeah.
[Jinman] Eso es difícil de hacer. Sí.
What if they see all that gold and just totally lose their mind?
¿Y si ven todo ese oro y pierden completamente la cabeza?
[Jinman] Right? They could do something crazy.
[Jinman] ¿Verdad? Podrían hacer alguna locura.
That's why you told me to lay off. Isn't that right?
Por eso me dijiste que me mantuviera al margen. ¿No es así?
That's gotta be it. STYLE ::cue()
Tiene que ser eso. ESTILO ::cue()
[sirens blaring]
[Sirenas sonando]
WARD 32
DISTRITO 32
[snapping fingers]
[chasquido de dedos]
Lee Dokyung. When's he getting transferred?
Lee Dokyung. ¿Cuándo lo transferirán?
[exhales]
[exhala]
Monday.
Lunes.
Let me see him real quick.
Déjame verlo un momento.
Well, unless you registered in advance, I can't-
Bueno, a menos que te hayas registrado con anticipación, no puedo...
Five minutes.
Cinco minutos.
[Kang groans]
[Kang gime]
I mean it.
Lo digo en serio.
Okay.
Bueno.
[Hocheol] No, no, no, no, no, no. Sit down, sit down, sit down.
[Hocheol] No, no, no, no, no, no. Siéntate, siéntate, siéntate.
I'm just here to talk.
Solo estoy aquí para hablar.
I promised Detective Kang I wouldn't be more than five minutes.
Le prometí al detective Kang que no tardaría más de cinco minutos.
[exhales]
[exhala]
[Hocheol] Looks like you're on the mend. You're up and walking.
[Hocheol] Parece que te estás recuperando. Ya estás de pie y caminando.
How's your head?
¿Cómo está tu cabeza?
Is it okay?
¿Está bien?
Like I've said before.
Como ya he dicho antes.
Unless my money and my safety are guaranteed...
A menos que mi dinero y mi seguridad estén garantizados...
I won't be telling you anything.
No te voy a decir nada.
[inhales]
[inhala]
Do you even know what's inside the casket?
¿Sabes siquiera qué hay dentro del ataúd?
[Hocheol] You do, don't you?
[Hocheol] Sí, ¿verdad?
[Hocheol] Maybe you knew from the start.
[Hocheol] Tal vez lo supiste desde el principio.
Or maybe your accomplice told you later.
O tal vez tu cómplice te lo contó después.
[Hocheol] It doesn't matter either way.
[Hocheol] Da igual.
I know why you're holding out.
Sé por qué te resistes.
I wouldn't have said anything, either.
Yo tampoco habría dicho nada.
[Hocheol] If I had a whole ton of gold in my hands?
[Hocheol] ¿Y si tuviera una tonelada entera de oro en mis manos?
I'd go all in. I mean, what else is there?
Yo lo apostaría todo. Es decir, ¿qué más hay?
[laughing]
[reír]
I did some digging.
Investigué un poco.
It turns out your accomplice was a woman.
Resulta que tu cómplice era una mujer.
She works at the airport. Yangpo, right?
Trabaja en el aeropuerto. Yangpo, ¿verdad?
[Hocheol inhales sharply]
[Hocheol inhala bruscamente]
[Hocheol] What's her name?
[Hocheol] ¿Cómo se llama?
Cha Yujin?
¿Cha Yujin?
[Hocheol] Your girlfriend.
[Hocheol] Tu novia.
[Hocheol] I was thinking I should stop by and meet her.
[Hocheol] Estaba pensando que debería pasar a saludarla.
[Hocheol] But if you don't wanna make things messy,
[Hocheol] Pero si no quieres ensuciar las cosas,
you should tell me what you know.
Deberías contarme lo que sabes.
Where's the casket?
¿Dónde está el ataúd?
[light shuddering]
[ligero temblor]
I don't know where it is.
No sé dónde está.
Does Ms. Cha Yujin?
¿La señorita Cha Yujin?
It's not her. She's got nothing to do with this.
No es ella. No tiene nada que ver con esto.
What are you getting at?
¿A qué te refieres?
She's not my girlfriend,
Ella no es mi novia,
and she doesn't know anything about the casket.
y ella no sabe nada sobre el ataúd.
Then who does know?
Entonces, ¿quién lo sabe?
[sharp breathing]
[respiración agitada]
[exhales]
[exhala]
[Hocheol] The thing is...
[Hocheol] La cosa es que...
...I don't have time for this.
...No tengo tiempo para esto.
By the end of this week, I have to find that casket.
Para finales de esta semana, tengo que encontrar ese ataúd.
I don't care what it takes.
No me importa lo que cueste.
So I was thinking about this whole thing...
Así que estuve pensando en todo esto...
...when I suddenly realized...
...cuando de repente me di cuenta...
...why even bother finding your accomplice?
...¿para qué molestarse en buscar a tu cómplice?
She won't admit to anything.
Ella no admitirá nada.
[laughs]
[risas]
Then you know what I thought?
¿Sabes lo que pensé?
I should just kill them all.
Debería matarlos a todos.
[Hocheol] Every single woman connected to you.
[Hocheol] Todas y cada una de las mujeres conectadas contigo.
One...
Uno...
...after another.
...una tras otra.
Girlfriend or not.
Con novia o sin ella.
[Hocheol] Whether she stole the casket or not.
[Hocheol] Ya sea que haya robado el ataúd o no.
Until you open up.
Hasta que te abras.
You understand?
¿Tú entiendes?
[Hocheol] You got till tomorrow to think it over and let me know.
[Hocheol] Tienes hasta mañana para pensarlo y avisarme.
If you don't talk, I'm really gonna kill them all.
Si no hablas, de verdad que los mataré a todos.
Starting with your girlfriend. STYLE ::cue()
Empezando por tu novia. ESTILO ::cue()
[shuddering]
[estremeciéndose]
[door slides open and closed]
[La puerta se desliza para abrirse y cerrarse]
[machines quietly beeping]
[Máquinas emitiendo pitidos suaves]
[Heeju exhales]
[Heeju exhala]
[grunts]
[gruñidos]
[indistinct chatter]
[murmullo indistinto]
[Jinman coughs]
[Jinman tose]
[cell phone vibrates]
[El teléfono móvil vibra]
[phone trilling]
[sonido de teléfono]
[phone vibrating]
[teléfono vibrando]
-[Jinman] Hello? -Hello?
-[Jinman] ¿Hola? -¿Hola?
-[Jinman] Hello? Ms. Kim?
-[Jinman] ¿Hola? ¿Señorita Kim?
[Hospital Announcer] Patient is in the ward...
[Locutor del hospital] El paciente está en la sala...
-Are you there? -[Heeju] I'm sorry I'm not available.
-¿Estás ahí? -[Heeju] Lo siento, no estoy disponible.
Leave a message and I'll call you back. Have a good day. Bye.
Deja un mensaje y te llamaré. Que tengas un buen día. Adiós.
[Hospital Announcer] Patient is in the ward.
[Locutor del hospital] El paciente está en la sala.
The guardian of patient Kim Minseo, please go to the reception desk.
El tutor legal de la paciente Kim Minseo, por favor, diríjase a la recepción.
[door clangs and creaks]
[La puerta retumba y cruje]
[exhales sharply]
[exhala bruscamente]
What were you doing here?
¿Qué hacías aquí?
Oh, not you.
Oh, tú no.
[car engines revving]
[motores de coches acelerando]
[cell phone vibrating]
[teléfono móvil vibrando]
-Hello? -[Dokyung] It's me, Dokyung.
-¿Hola? -[Dokyung] Soy yo, Dokyung.
[inhales]
[inhala]
One moment.
Un momento.
[Yujin] Are you still in the hospital?
[Yujin] ¿Sigues en el hospital?
[Dokyung] Yeah.
[Dokyung] Sí.
[Yujin] Are you crazy?
[Yujin] ¿Estás loco?
Why are you calling me?
¿Por qué me llamas?
[Dokyung] Take some time off work.
[Dokyung] Tómate un tiempo libre del trabajo.
[Dokyung] And go overseas for a while.
[Dokyung] Y me voy al extranjero por un tiempo.
Why should I?
¿Por qué debería hacerlo?
Is it the casket?
¿Es el ataúd?
[Dokyung] You're in serious danger.
[Dokyung] Estás en grave peligro.
You need to get out of the country right now.
Tienes que salir del país ahora mismo.
Fine.
Bien.
[Yujin] But first, let me just ask you one thing.
[Yujin] Pero antes, déjame preguntarte una cosa.
No one's listening in on our call, right?
Nadie está escuchando nuestra llamada, ¿verdad?
No.
No.
What on earth is inside of that casket?
¿Qué demonios hay dentro de ese ataúd?
If it's too difficult for you to say out loud,
Si te resulta demasiado difícil decirlo en voz alta,
just answer my questions. It's not drugs, right?
Solo responde a mis preguntas. No son drogas, ¿verdad?
[Dokyung] It's not.
[Dokyung] No lo es.
Is it gold?
¿Es oro?
[Yujin] The X-ray picked up a high-density material,
[Yujin] Los rayos X detectaron un material de alta densidad,
like metal.
como el metal.
No mechanical parts, like with firearms,
No tiene partes mecánicas, como las armas de fuego.
but more like solid masses of metal with no impurities.
sino más bien como masas sólidas de metal sin impurezas.
[Yujin] But you wouldn't have brought in something like iron.
[Yujin] Pero no habrías traído algo como el hierro.
Just tell me the truth.
Dime la verdad.
I promise I'll leave the country like you said.
Prometo que me iré del país como dijiste.
[Yujin] Fine, then.
[Yujin] Bien, entonces.
[phone beeps]
[El teléfono emite pitidos]
[exhales] STYLE ::cue()
[exhala] ESTILO ::cue()
[car alarm beeps]
[pitidos de la alarma del coche]
[indistinct chatter]
[murmullo indistinto]
TEMPORARILY CLOSED HAENGBOK PAWNSHOP
CASA DE EMPEÑOS HAENGBOK TEMPORALMENTE CERRADA
[gate clanging]
[golpeteo de puerta]
[keys jangling]
[sonido de teclas]
[exhales]
[exhala]
[Heeju] Shit.
[Heeju] Mierda.
[panicked breathing]
[respiración agitada]
[cell phone vibrates]
[El teléfono móvil vibra]
TEAM LEADER CHA YUJIN
JEFE DE EQUIPO CHA YUJIN
[phone clicks]
[clics del teléfono]
[phone buzzes rapidly]
[El teléfono vibra rápidamente]
[exhales]
[exhala]
[Yujin] If you don't call me,
[Yujin] Si no me llamas,
I'll tell the police that you're in Jeongsan.
Le diré a la policía que estás en Jeongsan.
[cell phone vibrating]
[teléfono móvil vibrando]
Hello?
¿Hola?
Is this how I get you to call?
¿Así es como consigo que me llames?
[Yujin] Are you avoiding me?
[Yujin] ¿Me estás evitando?
Uh, no, not at all.
Eh, no, en absoluto.
[Yujin] I'm on my way to Jeongsan now to see you.
[Yujin] Voy camino a Jeongsan para verte.
Why?
¿Por qué?
[Yujin] It must be hard on you,
[Yujin] Debe ser duro para ti,
considering what's inside that casket.
teniendo en cuenta lo que hay dentro de ese ataúd.
I can help you.
Puedo ayudarle.
Really? So what's inside of it?
¿En serio? ¿Y qué hay dentro?
[Yujin] You know very well what's inside it.
[Yujin] Sabes muy bien lo que hay dentro.
I'll call you when I get there. Let's have a drink somewhere quiet.
Te llamaré cuando llegue. Tomemos algo en algún sitio tranquilo.
[Heeju] Now there was one more person besides Woogy.
[Heeju] Ahora había una persona más además de Woogy.
One more person who knew I had the gold bars.
Una persona más que sabía que yo tenía los lingotes de oro.
I need to find out how much she know.
Necesito averiguar cuánto sabe ella.
[clocks ticking]
[tictac de relojes]
[♪ lively music playing]
[♪ Suena música animada]
[indistinct lively chatter]
[murmullo animado e indistinto]
[Yujin] Hi! You're here!
[Yujin] ¡Hola! ¡Estás aquí!
[Yujin] Whoo, whoo!
[Yujin] ¡Woo, woo!
Whoo!
¡Woo!
[Yujin] Hurry up! Hi!
[Yujin] ¡Date prisa! ¡Hola!
[Yujin] You didn't bring your car, did you?
[Yujin] No trajiste tu coche, ¿verdad?
Let's drink till we drop.
Bebamos hasta caer rendidos.
No, I drove here.
No, vine en coche.
Why? That's no fun.
¿Por qué? Eso no tiene gracia.
You said you wanted to talk someplace quiet.
Dijiste que querías hablar en un lugar tranquilo.
I did. It's better to have quiet convos in loud places.
Sí, lo hice. Es mejor tener conversaciones tranquilas en lugares ruidosos.
All right, go ahead, then. I can't be gone long.
Muy bien, adelante. No puedo estar fuera mucho tiempo.
Come on.
Vamos.
Sweetie, why are you so grumpy?
Cariño, ¿por qué estás tan malhumorada?
[Yujin] Keep this up and you'll hurt my feelings.
[Yujin] Si sigues así , me vas a herir los sentimientos.
[Yujin] The thing is...
[Yujin] La cosa es que...
...I spoke with Dokyung on the phone before I came here.
...Hablé con Dokyung por teléfono antes de venir aquí.
The casket.
El ataúd.
[Yujin] He asked me to help you get it out of the country.
[Yujin] Me pidió que te ayudara a sacarlo del país.
And he even told me what's inside of it.
Y hasta me dijo qué hay dentro.
What's inside of it, then?
¿Qué hay dentro, entonces?
Gold bars.
Lingotes de oro.
[Yujin exhales]
[Yujin exhala]
[Yujin] But don't take it the wrong way.
[Yujin] Pero no lo tomes a mal.
I guess he just thought I was more reliable than you
Supongo que simplemente pensó que yo era más confiable que tú.
when it came to moving them.
cuando se trataba de trasladarlos.
So where's the casket now?
¿Y dónde está el ataúd ahora?
I guess he didn't tell you that part.
Supongo que no te contó esa parte.
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm.
'Cause he told me I should just ask you.
Porque me dijo que simplemente te lo preguntara.
[exhales]
[exhala]
You're lying to me.
Me estás mintiendo.
He would never tell you about the gold bars.
Jamás te hablaría de los lingotes de oro.
He really did, though.
Pero sí que lo hizo.
[Yujin] But that's not important. You really are naive.
[Yujin] Pero eso no es importante. Eres realmente ingenuo.
It really doesn't matter who Dokyung loves or whether you believe me STYLE ::cue()
Realmente no importa a quién ama Dokyung ni si me crees STYLE ::cue()
or don't believe me. None of it matters.
O no me crean. Nada de eso importa.
[Yujin] If he gets his hands on the gold bars,
[Yujin] Si consigue poner sus manos sobre los lingotes de oro,
the outcome is the same for us.
El resultado es el mismo para nosotros.
It's Lee Dokyung.
Es Lee Dokyung.
He's not gonna share it with you or me or any other woman.
No lo va a compartir contigo, ni conmigo, ni con ninguna otra mujer.
I have Cha Yujin's location.
Tengo la ubicación de Cha Yujin.
Yes, in Jeongsan.
Sí, en Jeongsan.
Yeah. Yeah, the club in front of Gold Land.
Sí. Sí, el club que está frente a Gold Land.
[Jinman] But I have no idea if she's still there or not.
[Jinman] Pero no tengo ni idea de si sigue allí o no.
'Kay, good work.
Vale, buen trabajo.
[phone beeps]
[El teléfono emite pitidos]
That asshole has no fucking manners.
Ese imbécil no tiene modales.
It's Jeongsan.
Es Jeongsan.
Jeongsan Hobak Nightclub.
Discoteca Jeongsan Hobak.
Are you saying she's here in town?
¿Estás diciendo que ella está aquí en la ciudad?
She's probably looking for the casket.
Probablemente esté buscando el ataúd.
Share Cha Yujin's photo. Call the boys.
Comparte la foto de Cha Yujin. Llama a los chicos.
Don't just sit there!
¡No te quedes ahí sentado!
[nervous breathing]
[respiración nerviosa]
[Hocheol] Hey!
[Hocheol] ¡Oye!
Do it right!
¡Hazlo bien!
If anyone loses her, I swear I'll cut off one of their fucking ears.
Si alguien la pierde, juro que le cortaré una oreja.
Okay.
Bueno.
[cell phone vibrating]
[teléfono móvil vibrando]
SENT A PHOTO: PRESIDENT KO
ENVIÓ UNA FOTO: PRESIDENTE KO
[Gitae] Meet up at Jeongsan Hobak Nightclub. Find this woman.
[Gitae] Nos vemos en el club nocturno Jeongsan Hobak. Encuentra a esta mujer.
[cell phone beeps]
[pitidos del teléfono móvil]
[phone trilling]
[sonido de teléfono]
[motorcycle engine revving]
[Aceleración del motor de la motocicleta]
[Yujin] As of right now,
[Yujin] Por ahora,
the police suspect I'm Dokyung's accomplice.
La policía sospecha que soy cómplice de Dokyung.
And I'm pretending I don't know anything since it's currently better that way.
Y estoy fingiendo que no sé nada, ya que actualmente es mejor así.
I don't know how much longer I can keep this up, though.
No sé cuánto tiempo más podré seguir así.
[Yujin] Honestly, there's no reason for me to get on the suspect list just
[Yujin] Honestamente, no hay ninguna razón para que yo esté en la lista de sospechosos.
to protect you.
para protegerte.
You want the gold. Is that what it is?
Quieres el oro. ¿Es eso?
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm.
You got it. Bingo.
Lo tienes. Bingo.
The deal will be different.
El acuerdo será diferente.
You know what I think?
¿Sabes lo que pienso?
We should just split it between the two of us.
Deberíamos dividirlo entre los dos.
Hear me out.
Escúchame.
[Yujin] You're the one holding all the cards right now.
[Yujin] Tú eres quien tiene todas las cartas ahora mismo.
And since you are, you get to call the shots.
Y puesto que lo eres, tú tienes el control.
Do you wanna hand everything over to Lee Dokyung?
¿Quieres entregarle todo a Lee Dokyung?
[Yujin] Or do you wanna split it fifty-fifty with me?
[Yujin] ¿O quieres dividirlo a partes iguales conmigo?
[Yujin exhales]
[Yujin exhala]
[Yujin] Look, there's only one way this'll end if you go it alone.
[Yujin] Mira, solo hay una forma en que esto puede terminar si lo haces solo.
What'll you do? Hold onto the gold for months?
¿Qué harás? ¿ Te quedarás con el oro durante meses?
All the cops already know the casket is right here in Jeongsan.
Todos los policías ya saben que el ataúd está aquí mismo en Jeongsan.
And even if you were lucky enough
Y aunque tuvieras la suerte de...
to hold onto the gold all that time, then what?
¿Para conservar el oro durante todo ese tiempo, y luego qué?
The second Lee Dokyung gets out, he's gonna take it all away from you.
En cuanto Lee Dokyung salga, te lo quitará todo.
Even though you were the one who did all the work.
Aunque fuiste tú quien hizo todo el trabajo.
Here's what I think.
Esto es lo que pienso.
[Yujin] We have no choice.
[Yujin] No tenemos otra opción.
We have to get that casket out of here.
Tenemos que sacar ese ataúd de aquí.
Overseas.
Exterior.
The same way it was brought in through the airport in the first place.
De la misma forma en que fue introducido inicialmente a través del aeropuerto.
And can you think of anyone else who could pull that off better than me?
¿Y se te ocurre alguien más que pudiera hacerlo mejor que yo?
[Male Waiter] All right.
[Camarero] Muy bien.
Here's the fruit platter. And...
Aquí está la bandeja de frutas. Y...
...this one's on the house.
...esta corre por cuenta de la casa.
Have a fun night.
Que tengas una noche divertida.
[indistinct lively chatter]
[murmullo animado e indistinto]
[♪ lively club music playing]
[♪ Suena música animada de club]
[drink sizzling]
[bebida chisporroteante]
You wanna try?
¿Quieres intentarlo?
Oh, this?
¿Esto?
I heard this is what the kids call Rainbow.
He oído que a esto es a lo que los niños llaman Arcoíris.
'Cause it makes you feel great when you take it.
Porque te hace sentir genial cuando lo tomas.
Why don't you think it over some more?
¿Por qué no lo piensas un poco más?
I'm gonna go have fun.
Voy a divertirme.
[Heeju exhales sharply] STYLE ::cue()
[Heeju exhala bruscamente] ESTILO ::cue()
HOBAK, ADULT-ONLY ENTERTAINMENT NIGHTCLUB
HOBAK, CLUB NOCTURNO SOLO PARA ADULTOS
[Club Guard] Evening. Welcome in.
[Guardia del club] Buenas noches. Bienvenidos.
-[Gitae] Hey, Moonsu! -[Moonsu] Yes, sir.
-[Gitae] ¡Oye, Moonsu! -[Moonsu] Sí, señor.
[Gitae] Stand guard at the back door.
[Gitae] Mantén la guardia en la puerta trasera.
-[Moonsu] Yes, boss. -[Gitae] Okay.
-[Moonsu] Sí, jefe. -[Gitae] De acuerdo.
[Gitae] Stay sharp, everyone!
[Gitae] ¡Manténganse alerta, todos!
[All] Yes, sir!
[Todos] ¡Sí, señor!
[crowd cheering]
[Vítores de la multitud]
[♪ loud club music playing]
[♪ Suena música de discoteca a todo volumen]
[cell phone vibrates]
[El teléfono móvil vibra]
MISSED CALL WOOGY
LLAMADA PERDIDA WOOGY
[Woogy] Isn't this your boss?
[Woogy] ¿No es este tu jefe?
[Clubgoer A] Oh, move, move. Oh.
[Clubga A] Oh, muévete, muévete. Oh.
-[Clubgoer B] What's going on? -[Clubgoer B] Stay away from them.
-[Clubgoer B] ¿Qué está pasando? -[Clubgoer B] Mantente alejado de ellos.
[Clubgoer A] Stay out of their way.
[Clubgante A] Manténgase alejado de ellos.
[Gitae] Hey, you all have the photo, right?
[Gitae] Oigan, todos tienen la foto, ¿verdad?
-[All] Yes, sir! -[Gitae] Okay. Spread out and find her.
-[Todos] ¡Sí, señor! -[Gitae] De acuerdo. Dispersaos y buscadla.
[Henchman] Yes, sir!
[Esbirro] ¡Sí, señor!
[Gitae] Hold up. You two wait here.
[Gitae] Esperen. Ustedes dos esperen aquí.
[Both] Yes, sir.
[Ambos] Sí, señor.
-[Gitae] And you! -[Clubgoer A] Come on, come on.
-[Gitae] ¡Y tú! -[Clubgoer A] Vamos, vamos.
[Clubgoer A] We'll find another club.
[Clubsuy A] Buscaremos otro club.
[panicked breathing]
[respiración agitada]
[cell phone chimes, trills]
[sonidos de celular, trinos]
Hey, what's going on?
Hola, ¿qué pasa?
Where'd you get that photo?
¿De dónde sacaste esa foto?
Well, is it your boss or not?
Bueno, ¿es tu jefe o no?
It's her, right?
Es ella, ¿verdad?
Seems my company is after her. I hear she's in Jeongsan.
Parece que mi empresa la está buscando. He oído que está en Jeongsan.
What? Where in Jeongsan?
¿Qué? ¿Dónde en Jeongsan?
[Woogy] Uh, Jeongsan Hobak Nightclub.
[Woogy] Eh, discoteca Jeongsan Hobak.
Wait, where are you? Why is it so loud?
Espera, ¿dónde estás? ¿Por qué hay tanto ruido?
Hold on. Are you with her?
Espera. ¿Estás con ella?
You better get the fuck outta there!
¡Será mejor que te largues de ahí!
[indistinct chatter]
[murmullo indistinto]
[Woogy] I'm telling you, my company's looking for her right now.
[Woogy] Te lo digo, mi empresa la está buscando ahora mismo.
If you stay there, you're gonna get caught.
Si te quedas ahí, te van a pillar.
Shit.
Mierda.
[Woogy] I'm on my way to the workshop, okay?
[Woogy] Voy camino al taller, ¿de acuerdo?
You gotta just ditch her and get out.
Tienes que dejarla y largarte.
Are you there?
¿Está ahí?
Hello?
¿Hola?
Heeju.
Ey.
Hel-
Entero-
This is bad.
Esto es malo.
[breathing erratically]
[respiración irregular]
[indistinct loud chatter]
[murmullo fuerte e indistinto]
Excuse me. Excuse me, sorry. Sorry. 'Scuse me.
Disculpe. Disculpe, lo siento. Lo siento. Disculpe.
Ms. Cha, we have to leave now.
Señora Cha, tenemos que irnos ahora.
-Wh-What? Why? -They're here to get you.
-¿Qué? ¿Por qué? -Están aquí para atraparte.
[Yujin] Who? Who's here?
[Yujin] ¿Quién? ¿Quién está aquí?
[Heeju] What do I do? Ah, shoot.
[Heeju] ¿Qué hago? Ah, mierda.
What?
¿Qué?
-[Hocheol] Where d'you think you're going? -[Yujin] What's going on?
-[Hocheol] ¿Adónde crees que vas? -[Yujin] ¿Qué está pasando?
-[Heeju] This way. -[Gitae] Hold on a sec.
-[Heeju] Por aquí. -[Gitae] Espera un segundo.
Sorry. Sorry about that.
Lo siento. Lo siento mucho.
Shit.
Mierda.
He's gone.
Se ha ido.
[both breathing heavily]
[Ambos respiran con dificultad]
[gate creaking]
[crujido de la puerta]
This way.
Por aquí.
[both breathing heavily]
[Ambos respiran con dificultad]
[Yujin] He's coming! Run! Hurry, hurry!
[Yujin] ¡Él viene! ¡Corran! ¡Rápido, rápido!
-[Heeju] Here, I think it's this way. -[Jinman] Hey! Cha Yujin!
-[Heeju] Aquí, creo que es por aquí. -[Jinman] ¡Oye! ¡Cha Yujin!
[Yujin] Run! Run, he's coming!
[Yujin] ¡Corran! ¡Corran, viene!
-[Heeju] Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah, keys. -[Jinman] Hey! Hey!
-[Heeju] Oh, sí. Oh, sí, llaves. -[Jinman] ¡Oye! ¡Oye!
[Jinman] Cha Yujin! STYLE ::cue()
[Jinman] ¡Cha Yujin! ESTILO ::cue()
[Jinman] Wait! Cha Yujin! Open the door!
[Jinman] ¡Espera! ¡Cha Yujin! ¡Abre la puerta!
[Jinman] Hey!
[Jinman] ¡Oye!
No, wait! Stop!
¡No, espera! ¡Alto!
-Stop! Hey! -[Yujin] Drive! Drive!
-¡Alto! ¡Oye! -[Yujin] ¡Conduce! ¡Conduce!
No!
¡No!
[car engine revving]
[Aceleración del motor del coche]
[car horn honks]
[bocina de coche]
[breathing heavily]
[respirando con dificultad]
[Jinman] There's two of 'em?
[Jinman] ¿Hay dos de ellos?
[labored breathing]
[respiración dificultosa]
[both breathing heavily]
[Ambos respiran con dificultad]
Ah, shit.
Ah, mierda.
[Yujin] How did they know where to find us?
[Yujin] ¿Cómo supieron dónde encontrarnos?
-[Heeju] Ah, shit. -Do you think they're cops or something?
-[Heeju] Ah, mierda. -¿Crees que son policías o algo así?
Those guys aren't detectives.
Esos tipos no son detectives.
Huh?
¿Eh?
They're from Yes Money, a loan shark company around here.
Son de Yes Money, una empresa de préstamos usureros de por aquí.
They're the ones who smuggled the casket in.
Ellos fueron quienes introdujeron el ataúd de contrabando.
And Kim Jinman, the detective,
Y Kim Jinman, el detective,
this whole time he's been in on it, too.
Durante todo este tiempo, él también ha estado involucrado.
If we get caught by the cops, we go to jail.
Si nos atrapa la policía, vamos a la cárcel.
We'll be out in a year or two. But if we get caught by those guys...
Saldremos en uno o dos años. Pero si esos tipos nos atrapan...
...the gold bars won't be the only thing we lose.
...los lingotes de oro no serán lo único que perderemos.
We'll both lose our lives.
Ambos perderemos la vida.
[Yujin] Shit, no wonder.
[Yujin] Mierda, no es de extrañar.
There was something off about that fucking detective.
Había algo raro en ese maldito detective.
Oh, so that's why that asshole Dokyung said I should leave the country.
Ah, así que por eso ese imbécil de Dokyung dijo que debería irme del país.
[exhales sharply]
[exhala bruscamente]
So what do we do now?
¿Y ahora qué hacemos?
We have to be smart. There's no room for taking chances.
Tenemos que ser inteligentes. No hay margen para correr riesgos.
Okay, sweetie. You need to make a decision.
Vale, cariño. Tienes que tomar una decisión.
Is it me or Dokyung?
¿Soy yo o Dokyung?
Does that really matter right now?
¿Eso realmente importa ahora mismo?
If those guys back there catch us, then we're dead.
Si esos tipos de allá atrás nos atrapan, estamos muertos.
So what? I'll die whenever I'm gonna die!
¿Y qué? ¡ Moriré cuando tenga que morir!
Come on, sweetie.
Vamos, cariño.
Let's go get the gold together.
Vamos a conseguir el oro juntos.
[groans]
[gemidos]
[tires squeak]
[chirridos de neumáticos]
[gate rattling]
[Traqueteo de la puerta]
[keys jangle]
[sonido de teclas]
[lock clicks]
[clics de cerradura]
[door squeaks]
[la puerta chirría]
[door creaking]
[crujido de puerta]
Do you live here?
¿Vives aquí?
-Well, for the time being. -Oh.
-Bueno, por ahora. -Oh.
Didn't you say that you lived with your aunt?
¿No dijiste que vivías con tu tía?
She's in the hospital.
Ella está en el hospital.
[Yujin] Oh.
[Yujin] Oh.
So you're alone, then.
Entonces estás sola.
You can stay here until it's light out.
Puedes quedarte aquí hasta que amanezca.
Sleep in that room over there.
Duerme en esa habitación de allí.
And I'll come back tomorrow.
Y volveré mañana.
[Yujin] Why? Where are you going?
[Yujin] ¿Por qué? ¿Adónde vas?
To get the gold?
¿Para conseguir el oro?
[Heeju] Huh?
[Heeju] ¿Eh?
[electric sizzling]
[chisporroteo eléctrico]
[Heeju groans]
[Heeju gime]
[thuds]
[golpes sordos]
[Yujin exhales]
[Yujin exhala]
[chuckles]
[risitas]
[deep exhale]
[exhalación profunda]
[ticking clocks echoing] STYLE ::cue()
[sonido de tictac de relojes] ESTILO ::cue()
[Moonsu] Woogy, you asshole, you didn't show. Where are you?
[Moonsu] Woogy, imbécil, no apareciste. ¿Dónde estás?
[Woogy] I told you, I'm going to Daejeon to get President Jo.
[Woogy] Te lo dije, voy a Daejeon a buscar al presidente Jo.
Where are you?
¿Dónde estás?
You nearby?
¿Estás cerca?
Oh, yeah. That chick. Were you able to get her?
Ah, sí. Esa chica. ¿Pudiste conquistarla?
-Cha Yujin? -[Moonsu] We fuckin' lost her.
-¿Cha Yujin? -[Moonsu] La perdimos, maldita sea.
Look, the boss is here, and he's really pissed off, too!
¡Mira, el jefe está aquí, y está realmente cabreado!
Says he's gonna cut off everyone's ears, man.
Dice que les va a cortar las orejas a todos, tío.
That's her, right?
Esa es ella, ¿verdad?
The woman? She stole the casket.
¿La mujer? Ella robó el ataúd.
-Dokyung's accomplice? -[Moonsu] Of course she is!
-¿La cómplice de Dokyung? -[Moonsu] ¡Por supuesto que lo es!
So finish up whatever you're doing and get your ass over here.
Así que termina lo que estés haciendo y ven aquí.
'Kay, I'll be there.
Vale, allí estaré.
[flames roaring]
[llamas rugientes]
[phone beeps]
[El teléfono emite pitidos]
Whew!
¡Uf!
Shit, that's lucky.
Mierda, qué suerte.
CONNECTING CALL... HEEJU
CONECTANDO LLAMADA... HEEJU
[phone trilling]
[sonido de teléfono]
Ah, come on. Why isn't she picking up?
¡Ay, vamos! ¿Por qué no contesta?
[phone beeps]
[El teléfono emite pitidos]
[♪ suspenseful music]
[♪ música de suspense]
[exhales]
[exhala]
[tires rumbling]
[ruido de neumáticos]
[muffled shouting]
[gritos ahogados]
[cell phone vibrating]
[teléfono móvil vibrando]
[phone buzzing]
[sonido de teléfono]
[Woogy] Hello? Uh, Heeju. Where are you?
[Woogy] ¿Hola? Eh, Heeju. ¿Dónde estás?
-Why didn't you answer? -[muffled shouting]
—¿Por qué no respondiste? —[gritos ahogados]
You there?
¿Tú allí?
[Heeju shouting muffled]
[Heeju grita, pero su voz se oye amortiguada]
You hear me?
¿Me oyes?
I can't hear you. What are you saying?
No te oigo. ¿Qué dices?
[door opens]
[Se abre la puerta]
[Heeju grunts]
[Heeju abajo]
[Yujin] Poor baby.
[Yujin] Pobrecito.
You hid the gold bars in the mine, didn't you?
Escondiste los lingotes de oro en la mina, ¿verdad?
[Yujin] I saw coal caked all over the car tires.
[Yujin] Vi carbón adherido por todas las llantas del auto.
[Yujin] Here.
[Yujin] Aquí.
[Yujin] The coal mine at the end of National Route 7, right?
[Yujin] La mina de carbón al final de la Ruta Nacional 7, ¿verdad?
Inside the drift.
Dentro de la deriva.
[Yujin] Huh? Huh?
[Eugene] ¿Eh? ¿Eh?
-Right? -Ms. Cha! Ms. Cha, wait!
-¿Verdad? -¡Señorita Cha! ¡Señorita Cha, espere!
You won't find them on your own.
No los encontrarás por tu cuenta.
I'm the only one who knows exactly where they are.
Soy el único que sabe exactamente dónde están.
I'll go with you!
¡Yo iré contigo!
[Heeju] We can go together and split the gold bars, okay?
[Heeju] Podemos ir juntos y repartir los lingotes de oro, ¿de acuerdo?
Now you're saying that?
¿Ahora dices eso?
[Yujin] Well, too late. I don't need you.
[Yujin] Bueno, demasiado tarde. No te necesito.
I'll look all night if I have to.
Buscaré toda la noche si es necesario.
I'll just use a metal detector or something.
Usaré un detector de metales o algo así.
You really are naive.
Eres realmente ingenuo.
Do you honestly think Lee Dokyung and I keep you around
¿De verdad crees que Lee Dokyung y yo te mantenemos cerca?
because you actually matter?
¿Porque realmente importas?
[Yujin] It's like I already told you.
[Yujin] Es como si ya te lo hubiera dicho.
The only reason you were useful was because of the gold.
La única razón por la que eras útil era por el oro.
Not because we need you.
No porque te necesitemos.
-I beg you. -[Yujin] Yeah?
-Te lo ruego. -[Yujin] ¿Sí?
[gasps]
[jadeos]
[Heeju] Let's split them!
[Heeju] ¡Dividámoslos!
[Heeju gasping]
[Heeju jadea]
[Heeju wails]
[Heeju gime]
Please!
¡Por favor!
[muffled shouting]
[gritos ahogados]
[Yujin] You know, I was wondering what to do with you.
[Yujin] Sabes, me preguntaba qué hacer contigo.
[Yujin] I was a bit conflicted.
[Yujin] Estaba un poco indecisa.
But you just helped me make up my mind.
Pero me has ayudado a decidirme.
Yeah. Someone like you doesn't deserve the gold.
Sí. Alguien como tú no se merece el oro.
[muffled screaming]
[gritos ahogados]
[door opens and closes]
[La puerta se abre y se cierra]
[car door beeps]
[pitidos de la puerta del coche]
[car engine turns over]
[El motor del coche arranca]
[engine revving]
[Aceleración del motor]
[tires squeal] STYLE ::cue()
[chirrido de neumáticos] ESTILO ::cue()
[Yujin] Just drink this and never wake up.
[Yujin] Solo bebe esto y no despiertes jamás.
[Yujin] You think you're in love, but the truth is,
[Yujin] Crees que estás enamorado, pero la verdad es que...
you're leeching off of Dokyung.
Te estás aprovechando de Dokyung.
And even after your life is wrecked,
Y aun después de que tu vida esté arruinada,
you still cry out, "I was truly in love." Right?
Todavía gritas: "Estaba verdaderamente enamorado". ¿Verdad?
You've spent your whole life telling yourself that.
Te has pasado toda la vida diciéndote eso a ti mismo.
[Heeju whimpering]
[Heeju solloza]
[Yujin] Sweetie.
[Yujin] Cariño.
[Yujin] You really wanna go on living like that?
[Yujin] ¿De verdad quieres seguir viviendo así?
[Heeju groaning]
[Heeju gimiendo]
Just die.
Muérete.
[muffled shouting]
[gritos ahogados]
[coughing]
[tos]
[bottle clatters]
[sonido de botellas]
[both breathing heavily]
[Ambos respiran con dificultad]
Goodnight, sweetie.
Buenas noches, cariño.
Forever.
Para siempre.
[♪ tense music]
[♪ música tensa]
[coughing]
[tos]
[Heeju grunting]
[Heeju gruñe]
[muffled coughing]
[tos ahogada]
[lights buzzing loudly]
[luces zumbando fuertemente]
[Heeju groaning]
[Heeju gimiendo]
[grunting continues]
[Los gruñidos continúan]
[coughing]
[tos]
[gasping]
[jadeando]
[breathing heavily]
[respirando con dificultad]
[door creaking]
[crujido de puerta]
[labored breathing]
[respiración dificultosa]
[coughing]
[tos]
[car approaching]
[coche acercándose]
[gags]
[mordazas]
[Woogy] Whoa! Heeju!
[Woogy] ¡Wow! ¡Heeju!
You 'kay?
¿Estás bien?
Get up.
Levantarse.
Where're you going?
¿Adónde vas?
[gasps]
[jadeos]
[Woogy] Huh?
[Woogy] ¿Eh?
-I have to go. -Where you tryin' to go?
-Tengo que irme. -¿Adónde intentas ir?
The mine? Let's take my car.
¿La mina? Vamos a coger mi coche.
-You can't. Don't follow me. -Ah, come here!
-No puedes. No me sigas. -¡Ah, ven aquí!
[both grunting]
[ambos gruñendo]
-[Woogy] Okay. -[Heeju] Cha Yujin.
-[Woogy] Está bien. -[Suspira] Cha Yujin.
[both grunting]
[ambos gruñendo]
[gold bars clinking]
[sonido de lingotes de oro]
[grunting]
[gruñidos]
I heard everything on the call.
Escuché todo en la llamada.
That bitch, Cha Yujin.
Esa perra, Cha Yujin.
That woman really drugged the fuck out of you.
Esa mujer te drogó muchísimo.
[Woogy] And she's heading to the mine to steal the gold.
[Woogy] Y ella se dirige a la mina a robar el oro.
Hurry up.
Apresúrate.
She probably went to get her car.
Probablemente fue a buscar su coche.
If we go now, we can get there before her.
Si vamos ahora, podemos llegar antes que ella.
Fucking Cha Yujin. STYLE ::cue()
Maldita sea Cha Yujin. ESTILO ::cue()
[car engine revving]
[Aceleración del motor del coche]
[lights buzzing]
[zumbido de luces]
[car alarm beeps]
[pitidos de la alarma del coche]
[grunts]
[gruñidos]
[car door opens]
[Se abre la puerta del coche]
Huh?
¿Eh?
[car door closes]
[Se cierra la puerta del coche]
Cha Yujin?
¿Cha Yujin?
Yes.
Sí.
[chuckles]
[risitas]
Where's the casket?
¿Dónde está el ataúd?
Huh?
¿Eh?
[Yujin] Uh, the casket?
[Yujin] ¿Eh, el ataúd?
[Yujin grunting]
[Yujin gruñe]
[both struggling]
[ambos forcejeando]
-[gasping] - Fucking bitch.
-[jadeando] - Maldita perra.
I'm afraid I'm a little impatient.
Me temo que soy un poco impaciente.
So I don't have time to listen to your excuses.
Así que no tengo tiempo para escuchar tus excusas.
Sorry about that.
Lo lamento.
I'll ask one more time.
Lo preguntaré una vez más.
[Yujin gasping]
[Yujin jadea]
Where's the gold.
¿Dónde está el oro?
No! I-I didn't steal it! I didn't-
¡No! ¡Yo no lo robé! Yo no...
-What I took- -Really?
-Lo que tomé- -¿En serio?
-[Hocheol grunting] -[Yujin gasping]
-[Hocheol gruñe] -[Yujin jadea]
[Kang] Take this call.
[Kang] Atiende esta llamada.
[grunts]
[gruñidos]
[exhales] Hello?
[exhala] ¿Hola?
[Yujin] Do-Dokyung.
[Yujin] Do-Dokyung.
[Yujin gasping]
[Yujin jadea]
Yujin.
Yujin.
Captain, right now...
Capitán, ahora mismo...
...your girlfriend is about to take her last breath.
...tu novia está a punto de exhalar su último aliento.
Whether she lives or dies all depends on you.
Que viva o muera depende totalmente de ti.
Where's the casket?
¿Dónde está el ataúd?
[Yujin gagging]
[Yujin tiene arcadas]
[Hocheol] Fuck. Better speak up. She's about to die.
[Hocheol] Joder. Mejor habla. Está a punto de morir.
[Yujin screaming]
[Yujin gritando]
I don't know.
No sé.
[Yujin] The mine! The mine! The mine! It's in the mine. There's a mine.
[Yujin] ¡La mina! ¡La mina! ¡La mina! Está en la mina. Hay una mina.
[Hocheol] Which mine?
[Hocheol] ¿Cuál mío?
[Hocheol snarls]
[Hocheol gruñe]
[Yujin] Here.
[Yujin] Aquí.
[Yujin breathing erratically]
[Yujin respira de forma irregular]
[coughs] [Yujin] Here.
[tose] [Yujin] Aquí.
[breathing heavily]
[respirando con dificultad]
[Yujin] Wh-When you-when you get to the end of National Route 7,
[Yujin] Cuando-cuando llegues al final de la Ruta Nacional 7,
inside the very end is drift number eight.
Al final se encuentra el derrape número ocho.
That's where it is.
Ahí es donde está.
[Yujin] I'm sorry!
[Yujin] ¡Lo siento!
I'm sorry! I swear I didn't steal it! Please let me live! No!
¡Lo siento! ¡Juro que no lo robé! ¡ Por favor, déjenme vivir! ¡No!
Stop, no! Please no!
¡Alto, no! ¡Por favor, no!
[Yujin gasping]
[Yujin jadea]
[both struggling]
[ambos forcejeando]
Yujin?
¿Yujin?
[Hocheol snarling]
[Hocheol gruñendo]
[Yujin gagging]
[Yujin tiene arcadas]
[Hocheol breathing heavily]
[Hocheol respira con dificultad]
[phone beeps]
[El teléfono emite pitidos]
Heeju.
Ey.
[Dokyung] Heeju, it's me, Dokyung.
[Dokyung] Heeju, soy yo, Dokyung.
Park found out about the gold bars.
Park se enteró de la existencia de los lingotes de oro.
Move them fast.
Muévelos rápido.
[gold bars clink] STYLE ::cue()
[sonido de lingotes de oro] ESTILO ::cue()
[grunting]
[gruñidos]
Shit.
Mierda.
[bars clinking]
[sonido de barras]
[♪ dramatic music]
[♪ música dramática]
[Male Singer] ♪ Another day another hour ♪
[Cantante masculino] ♪ Otro día, otra hora ♪
♪ Free falling in my mind ♪
♪ Cayendo libremente en mi mente ♪
♪ I will find all of the reasons for leaving ♪
♪ Encontraré todas las razones para irme ♪
♪ When everyone around me's changing ♪
♪ Cuando todos a mi alrededor están cambiando ♪
♪ Everyone but me ♪
♪ Todos menos yo ♪
♪ All the things I thought I could be ♪
♪ Todas las cosas que pensé que podría ser ♪
♪ Are out of reach ♪
♪ Están fuera de alcance ♪
♪ I leave it all behind ♪
♪ Lo dejo todo atrás ♪
♪ As you fall in line ♪
♪ Mientras te pones en fila ♪
♪ I'm not expecting any light at your door ♪
♪ No espero ninguna luz en tu puerta ♪
♪ There's nothing left ♪
♪ No queda nada ♪
♪ Just the pieces of everything we could have been before ♪
♪ Solo los fragmentos de todo lo que pudimos haber sido antes ♪
♪ Evermore ♪
♪ Evermore ♪
♪ I don't feel it like I used to ♪
♪ Ya no lo siento como antes ♪
♪ Anymore ♪
♪ Ya no ♪
♪ You could find me in the dark ♪
♪ Podrías encontrarme en la oscuridad ♪
♪ Still calling through the night ♪
♪ Sigue llamando durante la noche ♪
♪ I leave behind all of the seasons ♪
♪ Dejo atrás todas las estaciones ♪
I've dreamed of ♪
He soñado con ♪
♪ But the water's rising over everything I've known ♪
♪ Pero el agua está subiendo sobre todo lo que he conocido ♪
♪ Drifting out here all alone ♪
♪ Vagando por aquí completamente solo ♪
♪ On your own ♪
♪ Por tu cuenta ♪
♪ So leave it all behind ♪
♪ Así que déjalo todo atrás ♪
♪ As you fall in line ♪
♪ Mientras te pones en fila ♪
♪ I'm not expecting any light at your door ♪
♪ No espero ninguna luz en tu puerta ♪
♪ There's nothing left ♪
♪ No queda nada ♪
♪ Just the pieces of everything we could have been before ♪
♪ Solo los fragmentos de todo lo que pudimos haber sido antes ♪
♪ Evermore ♪
♪ Evermore ♪
♪ I don't feel it like I used to ♪
♪ Ya no lo siento como antes ♪
♪ Anymore ♪
♪ Ya no ♪